<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Saiful Rijal</title>
    <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Saiful Rijal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/portfolio/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/portfolio/project1/</guid>
      <description>Image Classification with Deep Learning (On Progress) Guided project from Udemy: Complete 2020 Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning Bootcamp (with a few adjustments)
 Predict images using the pre-trained model from Keras package (tensorflow.keras.application. Includes image loading, pre-processing, loading models and predicting images. notebook: &amp;lsquo;Pretrained_Image_Classification.ipynb&amp;rsquo;. Image Classification with CIFAR-10 dataset. Include get the data, pre-processing, build neural network Keras model, visualising learning with Tensorboard (On Progress). notebook: &amp;lsquo;Keras_CIFAR10_Classification.ipynb&amp;rsquo;.  Link to github repsitory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Machine Learning Web App with Streamlit</title>
      <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/portfolio/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/portfolio/project2/</guid>
      <description>Build Machine Learning Web App with Streamlit and Python Guided project from Coursera: Build Machine Learning Web App with Streamlit and Python. In this simple project we are building a machine learning web app. In this web app we can:
 select a classifier (selecting a model: SVM, Logistic Regression, and Random Forest), adjust the hyperparameter for each classifier, Choose a visualization from the classification metrics. To know how to run python files in streamlit, please refer to the following link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/about/</guid>
      <description>Data enthusiasts who are open to opportunities to become a professional in a place that offers a positive atmosphere to explore Data Science and Big Data, as well as its application to greater benefits for society. As someone with a background not in IT or Statistics, I started getting to know and studying Data Science by taking bootcamps and related online courses. I realized that the development in the field of technology was very rapid, so in order to pursue the skills I needed, I had to instill a longlife learner mentality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Get in touch with me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/saifulrijal873/   GitHub: https://github.com/saifulrijal-ds   Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/saifulrijal_ds/   Facebook: https://web.facebook.com/saiful.rijal.90663894/    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saifulrijal-ds.github.io/portofolio-page/resume/</guid>
      <description>Saiful Rijal Data enthusiasts who are open to opportunities to become a professional in a place that offers a positive atmosphere to explore Data Science and Big Data, as well as its application to greater benefits for society.
SKILLS QUALIFICATION
Software Skills
 Python Anaconda; Jupyter Notebook, Spyder SQLite, PostgreSQL, DBeaver Tableau  Research Skills
 Data Analysis Data Science Machine Learning Natural Language Processing Data Visualization  Soft Skills</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
